ozealglasses.com 2019-06-03

# Privacy Policy, Shopping Security, T and C | Ozeal Glasses

### Customer Obligations

By placing your order to OZEAL the customer confirm:  
1 You should be aged 16 or over and are not registered blind or partially sighted.  
2 You should provide a valid prescription which is prescribed within 2 years (or 1 year if you are aged 70 or over) by a qualified person and has the correct details.  
3 You should make sure that all your info is absolutely correct, including address and contact details. We are not liable for any wrong info provided by you.

### Conditions of Supply

We should make efforts to ensure that all orders are fulfilled. Make sure that all goods sold on site are subject to availability, and all the descriptions and photographs on the items advertised are accurate.

We should have absolute discretion on whether or not to accept your order, and ask for a new prescription based on the advice of our Dispensing Opticians.

### Prices and Payment

Prices here exclude any shipping charges. Also, we will use best endeavors to ensure the accuracy of our prices, but we reserve the right to alter prices without notice.

Payment must be made by the Customer at the time of ordering, and we currently accept PayPal only.

### Shipping and Carriage

We will always endeavor to ship goods in the shortest possible time even the most complex prescriptions.

You should contact us if the goods are not shipped safely within a reasonable number of days; you will get a full refund or re-shipping if the non-shipping is caused by our fault.

### Site Contents

Unless otherwise noted, the Sites, and all materials on the Sites, including text, images, illustrations, designs, icons, photographs, video clips and other materials, and the copyrights, trademarks, trade dress and/or other intellectual property in such materials (collectively, the "Contents"), are owned, controlled or licensed by OZEAL TECHNOLOGY LTD (35 Ivor Place, Lower Ground, London, England, NW1 6EA)

Part of our transactions are processed by our online payment provider, APACPAY group.  
They operate in:   
Singapore, 3 International Business Park, Nordic European Centre, #04-01A, Singapore 609927  
Malaysia, 69-01, Jalan Mutiara Emas 10/2 Taman Mount Austin 81100 Johor Bahru, Johor  
United Kingdom, FIFTH FLOOR, 3 GOWER STREET, LONDON, WC1E 6HA, UNITED KINGDOM

### Return and Refund

You shall inspect the Goods as soon as the goods are received. When a claim of defect or damage is found you should first confirm the responsibility.

If it is our fault, you have the right to return the goods and receive a refund. If that happened, please contact us within 60 days. However, when damaged due to your fault, you are liable for the cost of remedying the damage.

### Force Majeure

Both parties are not liable for failure to perform the obligations if such failure is as a result of Acts of God (including fire, flood, earthquake, storm, hurricane or other natural disaster), war, invasion, act of foreign enemies, civil war.

### Governing Law and Jurisdiction

All the Terms and Conditions shall be accordance with the Law of the United States and submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the federal court.

### Your Right to Cancel

You have the right to cancel the order from you ordering until 7 working days after shipping for all stock items. Any custom made items (prescription lenses or tints) must be cancelled within 24 hours from the order being placed and we will make a full refund within 1-2 working days. If the Order has already been shipped, the customer will need to package the items and send them back to us and we will make a full refund upon receiving the package.

### For your protection

Our company is committed to protecting your privacy. We will only legal way (according to 'Internet Information Services' and other relevant data protection regulations) the collection and use of your information. Please note that your use of the site should comply with this privacy policy ("Policy") and published on the website's Terms of Use ("terms") requirements. This policy describes the following situation: what information we collect on the site, how we use and / or share that information and how to protect that information. Your use of this site signifies your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this policy in whole or in part, please do not use this site. Please note that this policy applies only to information collected through the website, does not apply to other methods or sources of information through access to information. This policy ensures that you provide to us are in the privacy of any information on the state and protected. To this end, we make provisions in the following areas: what information you provide to us, how the information will be used, under what circumstances that information may not be used. Without your express consent, we do not collect any sensitive information about you. We will make every effort to ensure the accuracy of the information at our disposal and in accordance with the information you provide to keep up to date. If you tell us the information is inaccurate, we will delete or correct it.

### Personal identification information

We collect personally identifiable information when you register or reply to a request for information voluntarily provided information. We can also collect your Internet Protocol address (IP address), through our server to help diagnose problems and manage the website. IP address means you use the Internet to your computer assigned number. Your IP address can also be used for a specific period to help identify you and gather broad demographic data. We may require you to use the site to provide e-mail address. Moreover, for the purchase of coupons, we may ask you to provide some or all of the following personally identifiable information: Name, Shipping address, email address, birth date, ID number, telephone number and payment details (such as credit card information).

### The use of personal identification information and sharing

All personally identifiable information should be based on the 2000 'Internet Information Services' and other relevant data protection laws and regulations to preserve. We use your personally identifiable information to us to provide you with relevant information, to provide you with better service and our own advertising. Our principle is not to our group than any other institution to sell or provide your personal identifying information, but in order to prevent fraud and investigation purposes required by law to provide for exceptions. Without your consent, we will never to any third party for marketing purposes and to disclose, sell or rent your personally identifiable information. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may share your personally identifiable information to our agents and subcontractors to help us in accordance with the provisions of this policy to use your data. For example, we may send information to the credit card service provider to complete the payment process. In addition, we always have the right to disclose personal for the purpose of proprietary information: (a) comply with applicable law; (b) response of government departments or quasi-government departments should be asked; or (c) to protect our rights or property, the Web site and / or other users of this site. Please note, in addition to the sharing of personally identifiable information provided, we may send your information to other countries, including countries outside US to send to, to meet the needs of our business and management. We will follow US network and information security provisions of the above information sent overseas. Some areas outside of US may not have relevant data protection laws, or the degree of protection of personal identity than the degree of protection provided by US. In submitting your personally identifiable information you acknowledge: Although we follow this policy to use your information, but we will not collect and process your data to third parties disclaims any responsibility for your data.

### Cookies

Cookie technology we use and by your browser on your computer to store data. Many sites use this technology, because Cookie enables website operators to complete many of the necessary work, including identifying the computer (and user) has visited this site. You can usually change your browser to prevent Cookie of this feature. However, if you change the browser, the service (and website) may not function properly. Cookie information stored on your system for identification. This technology allows us to provide efficient service, sure that the site visitor behavior patterns. In addition, to send ads to the site (if any) in the process of third-party advertisers or ad servers may be placed on your browser or recognize a unique Cookie file. The third-party advertisers or ad servers use the Cookie from the constraints of this policy, and by their own Privacy Policy. (Please note that minors under the age of 18 should not use this site.)

### E-mail

Please note that we may for the purposes of sending you e-mail and / or SMS: (a) as part of the Services to send you e-mail and / or short message. For example, we may be in the following cases to send you messages; (b) upon completion of your registration email and / or short message telling you the account details; (c) the services we provide to send you tips of mail and / or short message (especially if you have not used or shorter in the case); (d) request to send you information or vouchers; (e) sending information; (f) sending promotions e-mail and / or short message; and (g) to provide you with related services. However, we may send information for marketing or promotional e-mail and / or short message, we will then provide you refuse (or cancel) the service of choice.

### Information security and preservation

We will follow our internal security policy and relevant laws and regulations to properly hold personally identifiable information. We will stop using the data after 5 years to save the data. On the website and the information transmitted between users, although we will take reasonable measures to protect the information, but we may be unable to prevent third parties from unauthorized access to the information or inadvertently leaked during transfer. Contact the Web site the user should be aware of the risks that may exist.

### In some cases transfer

If any sale, merger, change of control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation, then we can decide on a third party to transfer, sell or transfer the information collected on this site (including but not limited to individual proprietary and other information).

### Customer Service

If you have any questions or concerns, please feel free to[ contact us](http://www.ozealglasses.com/ozeal-help-center#contacts).

### Choice and Opt-Out

If you no longer wish to receive the Company's promotional communications, you may 'opt-out' of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or by e-mailing the Company at service@ozealglasses.com.

### policy change

Please note that this policy constitutes an integral part of the website terms and you and we are part of an agreement. We can apply the law of this policy from time to time to perfect. Any changes to this policy will change in the contents of this website immediately. We will change the nature of the content, through our homepage, or e-mail (if you provide us with your e-mail) announced the change. In any case, after the change if you continue to use this site, you will be deemed to agree to such changes. If you do not agree to the terms of this policy and modify in whole or in part, please discontinue use of the site.

### Company Address

Ozeal Technology Ltd

35 Ivor Place, Lower Ground, London, England, NW1 6EA  

### Protection

We take security and privacy seriously by implement variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order, enter, submit, or access your personal information. We do not sell, trade, or transfer your personally identifiable information to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Secure Sockets Layer (SSL)**

Ozealglasses.com use 128 bit SSL, the strongest level of encryption commercially available, all online transactions of your sensitive information including password and credit card numbers are guaranteed to be 100% safe and secure.

GeoTrust® is the world's second largest digital certificate provider. More than 100,000 customers in over 150 countries trust GeoTrust to secure online transactions and conduct business over the Internet. With Geo Trust, you can feel confident shopping on our website!

**Secure connection**

When you make a purchase online, be sure to look for the little lock icon on the bottom of your web browser to make sure that your personal information will be protected by secure encryption. You can also check this by holding your cursor over the web page in question, clicking the right button on your mouse, and selecting 'Properties'. Then verify that the web address shown starts with an 'https'. The 's' denotes a secure web server.

At [ozealglasses.com](http://www.ozealglasses.com/), we only use "https" for our secure pages such like [Login ](http://www.ozealglasses.com/customer/account/login/) , [My Account](http://www.ozealglasses.com/customer/account/) , and [Checkout page](http://www.ozealglasses.com/checkout/onepage/). Pages that are only used for products or blogs will still use the regular "http" since no sensitive information is being passed through them.

**Cookies**

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings.

### Payment security

We use PayPal which is one of the most secure payment platforms in the world over a decade, to ensure your payment 100% secure. All of your sensitive information will be automatically encrypt and sent between your computer and the systems of PayPal to make sure your information is kept private. OZEAL does not record any of your payment information. 

PayPal accept all major credit and debit cards (Visa / Delta / Electron; MasterCard / Eurocard; American Express; Discover; Maestro) and PayPal, also you can pay eCheck via PayPal on our website. PayPal accept payment via mobile phone and other digital goods.

### Guarantee Return of 100% Satisfaction

We provide a 60-day no fuss return policy for our customers.

We will try our best to ensure you will be completely happy with your purchase on [ozealglasses.com](http://www.ozealglasses.com/). However, problems may occasionally occur. We strive to achieve 100% satisfaction for our customers.

We aim to make your shopping from ozealglasses.com with a safe and secure environment, and do our best to ensure you have the confidence for our brand and website.

### Gift card terms & conditions

  * Make sure you have correctly entered the recipient's email address so as to avoid the code is used by the wrong person.
  * Gift cards will be emailed directly to the recipient and the gift card code can only be used with the recipient's Ozeal account.
  * Not redeemable for cash.
  * Not transferable.
  * Not refundable.
  * If your gift card amount exceeds your order total, the remaining balance will be kept in your account.
  * If the order total exceeds your gift card amount, the rest will be paid by your PayPal or credit card.
  * Gift cards can only valid for a maximum of 12 months.
